So our ultimate goal is for any Tier 1 support question to be able to answer without human interaction.
That's the overall goal.
And then below that, there's an additional goal of time to resolution that we looked to influence and time to first response.
So you already know this, but Mach 1 can be an immediate response to a customer request.
But we have a set on a slight delay just to give it a little bit more of a human touch.
And so we have a set to, I think, four minutes.
Not a realistic human touch, but it's still four minutes.
And in the first few months after implementing Mach 1, our time to first contact dropped from multiple days.
Our team was that far behind on their support queue to four minutes.
It was immediate.
There wasn't a lag time in it.
So many of the inbound tickets were able to be handled by Mach 1 just from our launch that the ratio just shrank so far.
It was astounding.
It was absolutely astounding.